<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?>
<source>
<name>Hemi.worker</name>
<project>
<name>Hemi JavaScript Framework</name>
<url-title>Hemi JavaScript Framework Project</url-title>
<url>/Hemi/</url>
</project>

<package>
<path>Hemi.worker</path>
<library>Hemi</library>
<description>The worker is a managed wrapper for the HTML 5 DOM Worker.  Hemi Worker implements the <i>Hemi Module</i> service to inject the target worker script with the Module API, add a lightweight Psuedo Worker API for browsers that don't support Worker, and add a bootstrap to browsers that do support Worker so the Worker runs in the Hemi framework.</description>
Inside worker
Add Hemi framework
<static-class>
<name>service</name>
<version>3.5.1</version>
<description>Static implementation of the hemi.worker.serviceImpl class.</description>


</static-class>
<class>
<name>serviceImpl</name>
<version>3.5.1</version>
<description>The worker service provides a wrapper for adding the Hemi Module API to Worker scripts, and adding a lightweight wrapper for browsers that don't support Workers.</description>

<object>
<name>PsuedoWorker</name>
<description>A lightweight Worker implementation.  Includes all FrameworkObject members.</description>
<method virtual="1">
<name>onmessage</name>
<description>Invoked by the Worker via the <i>postMessage</i> method.</description>
</method>
<method>
<name>postMessage</name>
<param name="sData" type="String">Data to post to the worker.</param>
<description>Posts the specified message to the Worker.  <i>Note:</i> The wrapper does not currently convert objects into JSON notation.</description>
</method>
</object>
<method>
<name>NewWorker</name>
<param name="sPath" type="String">Path to the script which the worker will process.</param>
<param name="oContainer" optional="1" type="XHTMLComponent">XHTML Component acting as a container for the module.</param>
<return-value name="vWorker" type="Worker">A Worker or PsuedoWorker object..</return-value>
<description>Creates a new Worker or PsuedoWorker object, depending on browser support.</description>
</method>
oW.onmessage = this._prehandle_worker;
</class>
</package>
<index><description>The worker is a managed wrapper for the HTML 5 DOM Worker.  Hemi Worker implements the  service to inject the target worker script with the Module API, add a lightweight Psuedo Worker API for browsers that don't support Worker, and add a bootstrap to browsers that do support Worker so the Worker runs in the Hemi framework.</description><url>Hemi_api.html</url><url-title>API Index</url-title></index></source>