<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><source>
<name>Hemi.web.security</name>
<project>
<name>Hemi JavaScript Framework</name>
<url-title>Hemi JavaScript Framework</url-title>
<url>/Hemi/</url>
</project>

<package>
<path>Hemi.web</path>
<library>Hemi</library>
<description>Utilities for exploit mitigation.</description>
<static-class>
<name>security</name>
<description>A utility class for providing client support for exploit mitigation (requires corresponding server-side support).</description>
<property get="1" type="array">
<name>PageTickets</name>
<description>Array of tickets included with the Web page.  Tickets should be included for server-side requests requiring the presence of a ticket.</description>
</property>
<method>
<name>AddPageTicket</name>
<param name="sId" type="String">Ticket identifier.</param>
<param name="sUri" optional="1" type="String">URL used to restrict the use of the ticket.</param>
<description>Adds a new page ticket to the PageTickets array.  Used to reduce CSRF exploit potential.  A page ticket is a guid stored with the session, optionally for a specific server resource, and which may be required to complete an action.  Refer to the Hemi/Components/component.session.xml component, Account Manager 4 project, and Core Web project for a reference implementation.</description>
</method>
<method>
<name>GetSession</name>
<return-value name="oSession" type="object">Returns the session object from the registry.</return-value>
<description>Returns any session object added to the registry.  Hemi includes the Session component for use with Account Manager 4.  This can easily be updated to fit any desired server configuration.</description>
</method>
<method>
<name>IsAuthenticated</name>
<return-value name="bAuth" type="boolean">Returns a bit indicating whether the session includes an authentication bit.</return-value>
<description>Uses the Session Component to determine whether the current session has been authenticated.</description>
</method>
</static-class>
</package>
<index><description>Utilities for exploit mitigation.</description><url>Hemi_api.html</url><url-title>API Index</url-title></index></source>